I dream a lot, if there is any problem at all, then it gets resolved by then
[Music]
Ladies and gentlemen, question the
Constitution and welcome back to my channel
called Some Lots and today is the 7th, it's
time for the four children in the evening and
today in Yakshini, I showed you the last line
that I had gone to give my bike,
please get whatever
aloe vera is there in it changed, so today I will
pick up the bike and today itself I am going to tell you the complete
procedure that actually
if anyone has any problem with your bike or car, if
they have any claim for insurance claim, then
how to
claim it, you guys understand and the
last two blocks should be made for this thing only
and you guys are making this thing for this also,
so let's go now because the procedure is
not over yet, I have
not received the claim money yet, so for that it will take a little more
procedure, a little more time, which we will
tell you while we are on the way, first now we will
leave from here brother Ajay Janamejay Bhai Badhani  If it is there then
I should have Rs.6000 for that
because the Allah that is
lying there is Arun 57 58 drought so
basically I should have Rs.6000 which
I will give, I will go and
collect its bill during pregnancy, it will come later, so today I will
tell you what else I have to do next, we were in
bad shape till now, now we are open because
its yoga is very clear, so I
can take a chance because these clouds were here earlier
and have left by method and we have to go somewhere, we will
catch an auto from here and then leave, yes yes I do
n't know why, it was
good, it was well made, everything was given by me,
he gave the cycle to
Bhojpur, it happened that during the
training at Dadri railway station, Chakli
part of my life, my old days are very
much twin brother, its a bad
level story, for how many days I will
tell you in detail
that I am doing England, water is full
today, I don't know why a lot of police came from here
also, but this was also behind, a lot of police, but is there
anything, has Mike Reddy done it
or not, by the way, if so, that Yogi thing had happened, right
Who all are standing right now, the system is made in, it is just
5:30, actually when I came brother,
like it, but there was change, whereas the guy
called me and said that I will get this 5,000 in
change, no one, I have a
problem with just one thing, friend, I should have taken out the papers,
which was absolutely necessary,
send the insurance office there
because the thing is that
where you get the work done, the mechanic with whom
you are getting the work done in the agency,
they deal with which company, they
only treat them, the
rest of the network, for example, I had
insurance with New India Insurance, okay,
now what are these people, yes, like they are
working with ICICI Bank, so
what will they do for me, they will
make the documents and say, look, I will have to go and submit the file in the office,
I will do all the work, and
if I were with ICICI,
I would not have to do anything, so bring the bike and park it, get it done by
us, and do all this work yourself  If you do it then this is what happens
if you
people do not want me to work in the office for you to get your work done
then you should do one thing,
these are two options, if it reaches you then you can go with a
private bank or with the
insurance people, that is,
with a private company, otherwise talk to the agency from where you are
taking insurance, the
people themselves will get it done because what
maximum agencies do is they
spend more time with the private sector, because the private sector has a lot of
suggestions and very less impact, it is very easy, do
not work with them because they had the
entire system online, I do
not have to do anything and what happens in the government is that
brother take the papers and go, do this, do that,
50 things, he will come any time, brother, he will take
time and do that too for avenging
and the rest apart from this, I will not be
able to go today, let's wait till then, the
bike is standing like this, whatever is in it,
he will take time and come, he will put the masala on top of one and
then he will get it, after applying it, you will have to come to
Tarkulwa, this is called
Thursday, I also feel like meeting, why was there
no immediate hearing as to how it was
because it is someone's life
And his partner is like the wheel of a bike,
when both of them are not ready then
nothing is
going well in life, if there is something wrong with one Kabir, the
wheel or even the first one of them, then
his life becomes very tough, if it
goes on at all then it becomes very tough
and if there is any problem then it also comes to a standstill and so keep
your relationship smooth and m.s.
Tried to understand each other's features,
opinions and BJP fennel and wife, I have done my
best, it's time to leave now, I have bought my
bike at 6.15 and a
new album has been installed,
I am telling you the real thing, I have made some
changes in it, this hair is very much there, from where the
sound is coming, I have put this big one, it is
necessary because I had got it done myself in the front, so if I do it
quickly, it works,
jobs are available in my kitchen itself, time of my user is
five minutes old, boys, this GPS Honda
Dadri and
[music]
and brother's tube for Shubh set,
I taught, hey friend, where is this car in the middle,
officer, move away, hey friend, you,
Lukkad Das Mahant said in the Parliament,
Sodha, man should not, let's go back now to
see the world,
I have to go to the opposite side, so let's go,
bike Mata, swing, take the same
device light, that is ladies and gentlemen,
boys and girls, students, Monday, so how are you, I
gave it to you guys, in the last, which
you saw, which side was my bike  The aloe vera
juice was exchanged, the bill was to be taken
to the insurance company office in Shivling, I have two options,
either I courier it or I take it myself, I did
not make a courier system
because friend, look, if I had paid on Saturday or
Friday, if it was on Sunday, then I would not have found the address,
these people have
no idea about the fire, by the way, I got a copy
mailed, but I will have to take the still and go,
that Nabi said that I will have to pay it, so right now there
is a bill, a slim and a
photocopy of my passbook and in this fort,
brother, the vines, trees etc. in the fort, there is some
such system, so they cut one more
extra and send it, I have to submit it there, there is
payment about that, let's see
how long Rocky does this, so the one who has made the
pizza, brother,
he has sweated so much, it is getting very
hot and on top of that, to shoot the video,
I had to turn off the fan, I will have to turn
off the cooler, so let's quickly get out of the house
and before leaving for Ghaziabad,
definitely check the documents once,
this  In the district, their rape is the payment
receipt and this is the bail, so this has to be submitted,
this will remain with me for my work
and I have to get its photo taken and photocopied,
basically I will have to submit it along with this
and this Tulsi is wearing a dress, let's
go and do it
[sangeet] do it
[sangeet] it is done, at least make a
call friend I will bring the papers to the office quickly and we will
see and this is about the payment,
this is a problem in the government office,
right now as we are, first of all, when it is necessary to
give it, then that has reduced,
why, if I say on time, it will take at least 8
minutes, so brother, sir,
who is awake in the birth, so I am saying
that today it will take at least 8 minutes, I know you
and apart from this, right now what
I have
said here is that
if he had said that it is said to be
submitted in the office and the office person had gone through saying that he had to
bribe him and the report will be prepared for
his basic and secondary and
primary and mail, then all the
things will be written, so right now let's leave from here
because I am hungry, something more  I have not come
but I am here 04:30 MS It takes 2 minutes, tell me
crazy friend send it, the matter is over, come on, this takes
time, it will hardly take 2 minutes,
I did not stop for even a minute in the office upstairs, I will be
able to stop for a few seconds, chat chat
chat
[music]
that a [music] do it
[music] do it
[music] it
is done, it
is done
[music]